Hello everyone, welcome once again to
our new video today. In
this video, I'm going to discuss the
size of the mutual fund. I'll also discuss
which stocks
are listed on it. If you invest in this mutual fund,
what
returns would you expect? If you talk about it, the
return is 0.2%. If we talk about 5 years, the
return is 2.24% in 5 years. And if we
talk about annual returns, the annual return
is
19.10%. Please note that the returns
I've discussed with you here are
one-time, lump-sum returns.
If you invest in one go,
you'll get these returns. If
you invest through SIP,
you might get a different return.
I'll discuss this in this video.
However,
this is a very good hybrid
mutual fund, which is quite good, but the
market is down significantly right now,
so it's generating negative returns.
However, the way it's done,  If the market
goes up a little more or for a long time, then the chances of it increasing are
quite high. Talking about NAV, as of
today, its
price per nub is ₹1.7 paisa. Talking about rating,
it is a decent four star
rated mutual fund. The minimum SIP
amount in this is ₹5000000, that is, till now,
first of all let's talk about SIP that if
you do SIP at ₹000 per month in this mutual fund,
then in one year your money would have
accumulated ₹60000, you would have got ₹
890. You would have seen a negative return of around ₹3 per annum
because after September 2022, the
market has crashed a lot,
due to this, if we talk about 3 years, then
in 3 years your money gets accumulated ₹180000,
you get ₹
22291 and if we talk about 5 years, then in 5 years
your money gets accumulated ₹3 lakh, you get ₹
4621.84. Now let's talk about lump sum that
if you invest in this  If you had made a
lump sum of ₹1 lakh in a mutual fund, then in 1 year
you would have ₹
11130 lakh, in 3 years you would have ₹1556170 lakh
and in 5 years you would have ₹261957 lakh.
If we talk about holdings, the
total stocks listed in it are 90
stocks. If we discuss the top 10 and
their sector wise, then the first name that
comes is
IIC Bank Limited Financial
reliance.in Axis Bank Limited
Financial Bhartiya Tel Limited Communication
Lers & Turbo Limited Construction State
Bank of India is in the field of Financial and GI Saver
Gun. If we talk about their holding
analysis, then Equity Pay is
74.4, Debt Pay is 23.2 and Cash Pay is
2.4. If we talk about their equity sector location,
Financial Pay is 23 33.3,
Others 22.4 Energy 88.5 Consumer
Stock  8.2 Technology, 8 Construction, 6.9
Health Care, 6.4 and Capital Goods is
6.3, that is, if you
pay 5.3 but talk about advance ratio, then
its price to earning ratio is
22.6.5 and PV ratio is 3.46. If you
want to invest in this mutual fund,
then the minimum lump sum that you will have to do is ₹
000 and if you
invest through SIP, then you can invest
₹5000000
in 16 years, 22 in 5 years, 21.2 and annual
is 19.1. At the same time, the average return of this category, that is, of
a Hybrid
Aggressive Hybrid Mutual Fund is
6.4 in 1 year, 12 in 3 years, 16.6 in 5 years.
So from here we will see that this mutual fund has
always given returns higher than its category average in 1 year, 3 years or 5 years.
Talking about the expense ratio, their
expense ratio is 0.55 per
exit load. If you
withdraw more than 10% of your investment within 3 months, then you will have to pay an exit
load of 1%. Talking about the stem duty, the
stem duty is
0.005. Talking about the tax plan, if
you withdraw the invested money before 1 year,
then
you will have to pay a tax of 20% on your returns.
And if you withdraw your money after one year,
if the return is 125000 in one year,
then you will have to
pay a tax of 125%, that is,
you have to pay a tax of 20% on short term capital gain
and you have to pay a tax of 125% on long term capital gain.
If we talk about their fund house and investment objective, then
Mahindra Mutual Fund
ranks at number 28 in Total Assistance P India. Its
Total Assistance and Management
Mahindra Manulife Aggressive Hybrid
Fund Diet Growth worth Rs 4742 crore. This is a hybrid mutual
fund which has been launched by
Mahindra's.
You will have to pay an exit load of Rs 187 per 1 penny.
If we talk about the fund benchmark, its fund
benchmark is Chrysler Hybrid 35/65
Aggregate Index. So today in this video
I discussed with you
about Mahindra Manulife Aggregate Hybrid Fund.
We will meet again in the next video with
good information of this type of video.